

+84 795 902 054★ danganhhao.github.ioHo Chi Minh City, Vietnam

in dang-anh-hao✓ danganhhao8a3vts@gmail.com♠ danganhhao

About Me

My full name is Đặng Anh Hào, and I was born on May 16, 1998. I have successfully completed my education with a degree in software engineering. Currently, I am employed as a software engineer. I possess a total of 4 years of professional experience in the field of developing Android mobile applications, 2 years of experience in creating 2D games using Unity, and 1 year of expertise in cross-platform application development utilizing Flutter.

Education

Bachelor of Information Technology

University of Science – VNUHCM (HCMUS)

Bachelor's degree program

Aug 2016 – Oct 2020

I graduated with a bachelor's degree in Talent class a very good degree

Final Grade: 8.41/10

TOEIC Educational Testing Service (ETS)

English 2018

Total: 520

Technical skills

Programming Languages I am proficient in developing applications using the following program-

ming languages: Kotlin, Java, Dart, C, C/C++, Python, SQL Server

OOP, Design Patterns, SOLID I have a clear understanding of object-oriented programming principles

in application development and solid principles to ensure optimal appli-

cation performance

Development Platform Android native app (Kotlin/Java), Cross-Platform App (Flutter), 2D Game

(Unity)

Project Structure MVVP, MVC, MVP

Web Services Experience in web service integration (JSON, XML) with Retrofit, Okhttp3

Google ServicesI have experience working with Google services such as Firebase Ana-

lytics, Firebase Authentication, Firebase Realtime Database, Firestore,

and Firebase Remote Config

Game DevelopmentI have experience developing 2D casual games on the Unity platform

ADS, IAP I used to implement ads (Admob, FacebookAds, UnityAds) and in-app

purchases in mobile game applications

Others Django Framework, RestfulAPI, Socket. Tools: Git, SourceTree, Jira,

Slack, Trello, Clickup

Work Experience

FPT TelecomAndroid Developer

2019 – Present Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

• Developed Android application for watching movies, TV, and entertainment

Developed smart remote control application for FPT BOX C

Game Developer (Partime)

• Developed 2D-Unity Game

2021 – Present Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Projects

FPT Play

MEGADO

Android Application

- Customer: FPT Telecom
- Description: An Android application for watching movies, TV, and entertainment
- Team size: 8
- My position: Representative member
- My responsibilities: Research new technology, implement new features, and develop the user interface for the application
- Technologies: Kotlin with MVVM + MVI structure Hilt, Retrofit + Coroutine + RxKotlin, Navigation Component, Socket, FCM, Firestore

FPT Remote

Android Application

- Customer: FPT Telecom
- Description: A smart remote control application for FPT BOX C
- Team size: 5
- My position: Representative member
- My responsibilities: Research new technology, implement new features, develop UI, communicate with server
- Technologies: Kotlin with MVVM structure Hilt, Retrofit + Coroutine, Socket, Firebase

FPlayer

Android Library

- Customer: FPT Telecom
- Description: Player library that supports playing both DRM-protected and non-DRM content, download, change tracks, playback, cast functions based on ExoPlayer
- Team size: 3
- My position: Developer
- My responsibilities: Develop features for the player library
- Technologies: Kotlin OkHttp3, Coroutine, SQLite, Exoplayer

Wood Block Puzzle

Game Application

- Customer: Megado
- Description: Place blocks into the grid to complete the given tasks
- Team size: 5
- My position: Team leader
- My responsibilities: Research new technology, implement all features, handle game flow, build and deloy
 app
- Technologies: Unity, Firebase Authentication, Firebase RemoteConfig, Firebase Analytics, FCM, Admob, Facebook Ads, Unity Ads

Stickman Warriors

Game Application

• Customer: Megado

• Description: Defeat your opponents to win

• Team size: 5

• My position: Team leader

• My responsibilities: Research new technology, implement all features, handle game flow, build and deloy

• Technologies: Unity, Firebase Authentication, Firebase RemoteConfig, Firebase Analytics, FCM, Admob, Facebook Ads, Unity Ads

Social Network

f anh.hao.haugiang

o qboydang

anganhhao8a3vts